Okay, so this is the second leg that we did, and this is the one that we cut off, it has the seam binding on it or hem tape, whatever you want to call it.
And this is just a little review of what we did on the other leg basically.
We're going to pin this up right where we want it.
And on the other leg, let's see on this one.
Actually I had used the gray thread, and now that I'm pinning this up, looking at it, I think I might just use some black thread that will match my hem tape, and it will make it look really nice and professional, just in case somebody wants to look inside of your pant leg and see how it's done.
Okay, so let me get my needle out, and enough thread to go around the leg.
And I like to use a really sharp needle on blue jeans just because, if you use a dull one it's going to be really hard to grab those little pieces.
Okay, so, I'm going to start right here where these have overlaps, and I'm going to, I'm just going to move that thing out of the way.
This is one of the few things that you kind of need to know about steam binding.
There we go.
And I'm just going to grab the pants, the lower layer and the fold, all at once, and I'm actually going to make several tacks just to go through this, because I don't want that to come apart.
I don't think it's going to, I did like 4, so.
And I showed you how to do a whip stitch earlier, so let's just review.
You grab a little piece, go right through the side of the binding, and it's basically just like it says, a whip stitch, it's a blind stitch.
When you flip it over you can't see it on the other side.
There we go.
And we're almost finished with this.